[♪♪♪]
[人群叫囂,歡呼]
[crowd clamouring, cheering]
[遠距離咚咚]
[thumping in distance]
[傑姆呻吟,褲子]
[Jem groans, pants]
[皮爾斯咕嚕咕嚕]
[Pearce grunting]
[咕嚕聲]
[grunts]
[鈴鐺叮噹聲]
[bell dings]
時間。時間,時間。
Time. Time, time.
[褲子、髒話]
[pants, slurps]
[呼吸沉重]
[breathes heavily]
[♪♪♪]
嘿,你好。
Oi, oi.
[喘氣,咕嚕]
[gasps, grunts]
看著我。看著我。
Look at me. Look at me.
-你沒事吧？
-[褲子] 是的。
-You all right?
-[pants] Yeah.
[咕嚕聲]
[grunts]
[人群歡呼]
[crowd cheering]
[褲子,咕嚕聲]
[pants, grunts]
[呻吟,咕嚕聲]
[groans, grunts]
[咕嚕聲]
[grunts]
[♪♪♪]
[傑克深吸氣]
[Jack exhales deeply]
[人群叫囂]
[crowd clamouring]
[戰士呻吟,咕嚕聲]
[fighters groans, grunts]
不是沒有地方適合你,小夥子。
Ain't no place for you, boy.
那是我的爺爺！
That's my grandpa!
-[本呻吟]
-[咕嚕聲]
-[Ben groans]
-[grunts]
[本呻吟]
[Ben groaning]
傑克·斯拉克的血,嗯？
Jack Slack's blood, eh?
-[咕嚕聲]
-[呻吟]
-[grunts]
-[groans]
知道了,嗯？他是個屁。
Got him, eh? He's a fart.
把他扔到那裡去,小夥子們。
Throw him up there, lads.
[本呻吟]
[Ben groaning]
[傑克咕嚕咕嚕]
[Jack grunting]
加油！看啊。
Come on! Look at that.
[咕嚕聲]
[grunts]
[咕嚕聲,褲子]
[grunts, pants]
明白了
你有一些經驗。
I see
you've had some experience.
[斯皮茨]
[spits]
-[呻吟]
-[咕嚕聲]
-[groans]
-[grunts]
[人群吹口哨,歡呼]
[crowd whistling, cheering]
哦！他是一個強硬的“不”。
Oh! He's a tough ‘un.
=[歡呼]
-[咕嚕聲]
=[cheers]
-[grunts]
加油！
這是一個艱難的『un。
Come on!
Here's a hard ‘un.
[呻吟]
[groans]
[傑克咕嚕聲]
[Jack grunts]
不是嗎？不是嗎？
Ain’t ya? Ain’t ya?
-[呻吟]
-[乾杯]
-[groans]
-[cheers]
[人群歡呼,口哨聲]
[crowd cheers, whistles]
[♪♪♪]
[深呼氣]
[exhales deeply]
沒什麼可指望的。
Not much to count for.
馬車被停了下來
在他們再次進入的路上。
Carriages were stopped
on their way in again.
[鳥兒嘰嘰
[birds chirping]
把你的手伸出來,孩子。
Put your hand out, boy.
[硬幣叮噹聲]
[coins clanking]
皮爾斯:
英俊的小夥子。
不過有點瘦。
PEARCE:
Handsome lad.
Bit skinny, though.
是的。
Yeah.
他是個流浪漢。
He's a runt.
[深呼氣]
[exhales deeply]
就像他的父親一樣。
Just like his father was.
哦,喬。
這就是我一直在等待的。
Oh, Joe.
That's what I was waiting for.
（笑）
[laughs]
[馬鄰]
[horses neighs]
-我告訴你什麼？
-但是,媽！
-What’d I tell you?
-But, Ma!
瑪麗:
保持你的舌頭！回家。
MARY:
Hold your tongue! Get home.
他喜歡看
他的爺爺打架,瑪麗。
He likes watching
his granddad fight, Mary.
就像你一樣
當你是他的年齡。
Like you did
when you was his age.
那是過去的事情了。
That's in the past.
他沒有在他身上得到它
做你做過的事情。
He ain't got it in him
to do what you did.
他只是一個男孩。
He's just a boy.
給他時間。
Give him time.
我告訴過你。。。
I told you...
我不想讓他在你的世界裡。
I don't want him in your world.
你遠離他。
You stay away from him.
他是一個貝爾徹,瑪麗。
He's a Belcher, Mary.
你,我,傑姆...
You, me, Jem...
我們都被切割了
從同一塊布。
we're all cut
from the same cloth.
你讓他獨自一人。
You leave him alone.
[深呼吸]
[breathes deeply]
祝福我們...
Bless us...
哦,主...
Oh, Lord...
作為食物的禮物
我們即將收到。
for the gift of food
we are about to receive.
我們來找你...
We come to You...
為了力量...
for strength...
知道你是
我們的供應商。
knowing that You are
our provider.
阿門。
Amen.
怎麼了,吉利？
What's the matter, Gilly?
這裡。
Here.
有我的,寵物。
Have mine, pet.
這就是我們得到的一切。
It's all we got.
[人群叫囂]
[crowd clamouring]
加油。下注。
Come on. Place your bets.
下注。
Place your bets.
[人群叫囂]
[crowd clamouring]
預訂人:
[含糊不清]
BOOKIE:
[speaks indistinctly]
你在這裡幹什麼？
What are you doing here?
我想看看雞。
I wanted to see the chickens.
雞？
Chickens?
（笑）
[laughs]
你好？
Oi?
我會把它放在蘭斯洛特身上。
I'll put that on Lancelot.
我在蘭斯洛特上有一個很大的問題。
I've got a big oner on Lancelot.
誰能和他相提並論？加油。
Who can match him? Come on.
當我們贏了...
When we win...
我會給你死鳥
帶回家。
I'll give you the dead bird
to take home.
是的！
Yes!
[仿雞]
[imitates chicken]
[傑克咯咯笑]
[Jack chuckling]
[人群歡呼]
[crowd cheers]
加油！
Come on!
來吧,蘭斯洛特。
Come on, Lancelot.
[公雞咯]
[rooster clucks]
千斤頂:
抓住他！
JACK:
Get him!
來吧,蘭斯洛特！
Come on, Lancelot!
[公雞咯咯叫]
[roosters clucking]
現在就來吧！
Come on now!
預訂人:
熱刺是贏家！
BOOKIE:
Hotspur is the winner!
Hotspur是贏家。
Hotspur is the winner.
嘿！
Hey!
我知道你修復了那場戰鬥。
I know you fixed that fight.
我想要回我的錢。
I want my money back.
賭注就是賭注,傑克。
A bet's a bet, Jack.
我想要回我的錢。
I want my money back.
你知道規則,夥計。
You know the rules, mate.
你為什麼不加倍努力
在下一個？
Why don't you double up
on the next one?
我的眼睛盯著你。
I've got my eyes on you.
也許你應該保持你的眼睛
在男孩身上。
Maybe you should keep your eyes
on the boy.
嘿,這是怎麼回事？
-[傑克咯咯笑]
-Oi!
-[Jack chuckling]
回來吧,你這個小傢伙！
Come back here, you little runt!
（笑）
[laughs]
瑪麗:
我告訴過你不要拿任何東西
從他那裡,傑姆。
MARY:
I told you not to take anything
from him, Jem.
過來這裡。
Come here.
你不想要血
在你的手上。
You don't want blood
on your hands.
[抽泣]
[sobs]
[模糊的喋喋不休]
[indistinct chatter]
瑪麗:
爸爸。
MARY:
Dad.
你在這裡做什麼？
What you doin’ here?
我需要和你談談。
I need to talk with you.
右。坐。
Right. Sit.
加油。坐。
Come on. Sit.
和你的老頭一起喝一口。
Have a swig with your old man.
我是來談論傑姆的。
I came to talk about Jem.
他需要...
He needs...
愛
love,
恩。
kindness.
他不需要
沒有教訓...
He don't need
no lessons in...
來自你的痛苦。
pain from you.
我沒有對他造成任何傷害。
I'm not doing him any harm.
他需要...
He needs...
父親。
a father.
他需要...
He needs...
一個他可以仰望的人。
someone he can look up to.
你需要告訴他停下來
來到這裡。
You need to tell him to stop
coming here.
不。
No.
不,他需要一個男人...
No, he needs a man...
教他紀律
等等。
to teach him about discipline
and the like.
他不會學到的
從你那裡。
He ain't gonna learn that
from you.
我付了衣服
在你的背上。
I paid for the clothes
on your back.
我付了十字架
在你的脖子周圍。
And I paid for the cross
around your neck.
我每天都在工作
我的生活。
I have worked every day
of my life.
你把它全部喝掉。
And you drink it all away.
不是嗎？
Don't you?
你想讓我說什麼
給男孩,瑪麗？
What do you want me to say
to the boy, Mary?
他是你的兒子。
He's your son.
只是遠離就是一切。
Just stay away is all.
不要鼓勵他。
Don't encourage him.
如果你告訴他遠離,
他會遠離的。
If you tell him to stay away,
he'll stay away.
[♪♪♪]
拜託了,爸爸。
Please, Dad.
[馬兒近在咫尺]
[horses neighing]
哎呀,貝爾徹！
Oi, Belcher!
多麼漂亮的衣服
你到了,貝爾徹。
What a pretty outfit
you've got there, Belcher.
去碼頭,是嗎？
Off to the docks, are we?
看看他。小莫莉。
Look at him. Little molly.
這是什麼,貝爾徹？嗯？
And what's this, Belcher? Hmm?
適合媽媽的東西
櫥櫃？
Something for your ma's
cupboard?
我們都知道她是她的最愛
與水手們。
We all know she's a favourite
with the sailors.
[庫利咯咯笑]
[Cully chuckles]
來吧,說點什麼。
Go on, say something.
我敢。
I dare you.
-你的牙齒像狗屎一樣臭。
-給他種一個,阿奇。
-Your teeth stink like shit.
-Plant him one, Archey.
-是的,夥計。來吧,現在。
-哦。看看他。
-Yeah, mate. Come on, now.
-Ooh. Look at him.
他認為自己可以打架
就像他的爺爺一樣。
He thinks he can fight
like his grandad.
他甚至不擅長。
He weren't even good.
[呻吟]
[groans]
你死了,貝爾徹！
You're dead, Belcher!
足夠！
Enough!
走吧,讓你走吧,
Go on, get you going,
或者我會去拜訪
致你們的每一位父親。
or I'll pay a visit
to each of your fathers.
把你站直,小夥子。
Stand you up straight, boy.
暴力與採取同等重要的關係
痛苦,因為它正在施加它。
Violence is as much about taking
pain as it is inflicting it.
媽知道嗎
你在這裡嗎？
Does your mother know
you're here?
她不知道的不多。
Ain't much she don't know.
當你戰鬥時...
When you fight...
一隻手跟著另一隻手。
one hand follows the other.
一個拳頭的男人
用雙手...
A man who punches
with both hands...
並繼續打孔...
and keeps punching...
這就是戰鬥機
誰會贏。
that's the fighter
who's gonna win.
哭泣'...
Cryin'...
這無濟於事。
it's ain't gonna help.
在生活中...
In life...
不知道一個給兩個狗屎
關於你。
don't no one give two shits
about you.
唯一的辦法
保護自己
The only way
to protect yourself
就是要攻擊。
is to attack.
戰鬥。
To fight.
你能教我更多嗎？
Can you teach me more?
（笑）
[laughs]
我能教你更多嗎？
Can I teach you more?
好吧,也許是喝一杯,對吧？
Well, perhaps over a drink, huh?
瑪麗。
Mary.
我需要錢。
I need money.
慚愧呀。
Shame on ya.
安靜,孩子。
Quiet, child.
你在神的家裡。
You're in the house of God.
看看你。
Look at ya.
你是一個恥辱。
You're a disgrace.
不要心懷怨恨。
Don't bear grudges.
你的丈夫...
Your husband...
他不會回來的
he ain't coming back.
你什麼都沒做
但給我們帶來恥辱。
You ain't done nothing
but bring shame on us.
你有一張嘴在你身上。
You have a mouth on ya.
不是嗎,瑪麗？
Haven't you, Mary?
就像媽一樣。
Just like your mother.
你看起來很像她
從這個角度來看。
You look a lot like her
in this light.
[顫抖地呼吸]
[breathes shakily]
離開。離開我們吧。
Leave. Just leave us.
我會的。
I will.
你這個醉酒的混蛋。
You drunken bastard.
[顫抖地呼吸]
[breathes shakily]
在這裡,一隻手
跟在另一個後面。
Here, one hand
follows the other.
謝謝你,主...
Thank you, Lord...
作為您的禮物。
for your gift.
[♪♪♪]
哦,他是我的
你知道他是我的。
Oh, he’s mine
and you know he’s mine.
[笑]
[chuckles]
你來了,愛。繼續。
Here you go, love. Go on.
（笑）
[laughs]
[♪♪♪]
[金屬叮噹聲]
[metal clanking]
擊中中心,貝爾徹！
Strike it in the center, Belcher!
有一排男人
取代您的位置
There's a line of men
to take your place
如果你不能拉動你的體重。
if you can't pull your weight.
[咕嚕聲,褲子]
[grunts, pants]
[♪♪♪]
[金屬嘶嘶聲]
[metal sizzles]
問題,傑姆·貝爾徹？
Problem, Jem Belcher?
沒有,先生。
No, sir.
至少,它是某種東西。
At least, it's something.
是的。
Yeah.
加油。
Come on.
[模糊的喋喋不休]
[indistinct chatter]
新鮮的蛋撻。
Fresh custard tarts.
[含糊不清]
[speaks indistinctly]
嘿,這是怎麼回事？
-是他！
-Oi!
-It was him!
-學習一些禮儀！
- 不,不！
-Learn some manners!
-No, no!
不是我。是他！
It wasn't me. It was him!
學習一些禮儀。
Learn some manners.
[兩個笑聲]
[both chuckles]
你呢,先生？
我能讓你感興趣嗎？不是嗎？
What about you, sir?
Can I interest you-- no?
-你想跳舞嗎？
- 不！
-Do you wanna dance?
-No!
-來吧！
- 不！
-Come on!
-No!
跳舞！
Dance!
[笑]
[chuckles]
停。停！
Stop. Stop!
[笑]
[chuckles]
[人群歡呼]
[crowd cheering]
湯姆:
嘿,傑姆。
TOM:
Hey, Jem.
不過,來這裡吧！
Come here, though!
加油。
Come on.
[鮑勃咕嚕咕嚕]
[Bob grunting]
[吟遊詩人咕嚕咕嚕]
[Bard grunting]
[呻吟]
[groans]
[咕嚕聲]
[grunts]
[人群歡呼]
[crowd cheering]
[鮑勃咆哮]
[Bob growling]
不敗者
鮑勃「黑鬍子」布里頓
The undefeated
Bob "Blackbeard" Britton
粉筆又一次勝利！
chalks up another victory!
[人群歡呼]
[crowd cheering]
RINGLEADER （OS/ON）
加油！
RINGLEADER (OS/ON)
Come on!
任何其他偽裝者會
到他的王位
Will any other pretender
to his throne
請向前邁進？
please step forward?
它歸於我
親自提供...
It behoves me
to personally offer up...
我的整個錢包...
my whole purse...
給任何能活下去的男人
一輪
to any man who can last
one round
與鮑勃「黑鬍子」布里頓！
with Bob "Blackbeard" Britton!
[人群歡呼,鼓掌]
[crowd cheers, applauds]
這是很多硬幣。
That's a lot of coin.
這裡。
Here.
傑姆,你在做什麼？
Jem, what are you doing?
我們需要這些硬幣。
We need those coins.
你在開玩笑嗎？
Are you joking?
他會殺了你。
He'll kill you.
兒子,你叫什麼名字？
What's your name, son?
傑姆。
Jem.
吉姆？
Jim?
傑姆·貝爾徹。
Jem Belcher.
我是個笨蛋。
I'm the bummer.
我相信你會給我們
一場精彩的表演。
I'm sure you're gonna give us
a great show.
女士們先生們！
Ladies and gentlemen!
一個傑姆·貝爾徹！
One Jem Belcher!
[人群歡呼]
[crowd cheers]
毫米？
Mm?
原石中的鑽石...
A diamond in the rough...
如果我曾經見過一個。
if ever I saw one.
我的錢花在瘦弱的傢伙身上。
My money's on the skinny fellow.
多少？
How much?
我會打這個賭注。
I'll take that bet.
先生。
Gentlemen.
到你的角落。
To your corners.
時間！
Time!
[咕嚕聲]
[grunts]
進去。
Get in there.
[咕嚕聲]
[grunts]
[人群喧囂]
[crowd clamours]
[咕嚕聲]
[grunts]
傑姆,停下。他要殺了你。
Jem, stop. He's gonna kill ya.
[咕嚕聲]
[grunts]
[人群驚呼]
[crowd exclaims]
[人群歡呼]
[crowd cheers]
不,回去吧！
No, get back in!
[咕嚕聲]
[grunts]
美麗。
Beautiful.
來吧,傑姆！
Come on, Jem!
[咕嚕聲、呻吟聲]
[grunts, groans]
[咕嚕聲]
[grunts]
湯姆:
是的！來吧,傑姆。
TOM:
Yes! Come on, Jem.
[傑姆咕嚕聲]
[Jem grunts]
[褲子]
[pants]
（笑）
[laughs]
[清嗓子]
[clears throat]
我的硬幣在哪裡？
Where's my coins?
你為什麼不來為我工作？
Why don't you come work for me?
你可以有一個
每周。
You can have one of these
every week.
[笑]
[chuckles]
-我們很好。
-[笑聲]
-We’re good.
-[chuckles]
[笑]
[chuckles]
鑽石原石。
Diamond in the rough.
[傑姆咕嚕聲]
[Jem grunts]
關門。
Close the door.
湯姆！
Tom!
你關上門！
You close the door!
只需關閉它。
Just close it.
[硬幣嘎嘎作響]
[coins rattling]
什麼？
What?
如果我發現你偷了這個...
If I find out you stole this...
別傻了,媽媽。
Don't be silly, Ma.
我們贏得了它的好處和適當。
We earned it good and proper.
[海鷗吱吱叫]
[seagulls squawking]
[海浪撞擊]
[waves crashing]
[咕嚕聲]
[grunts]
好吧,你花了你的時間。
Well, you took your time.
你不能只是走開
從喊叫
You can't just walk away
from a shout
當有人給你一杯飲料時。
when someone offers you a drink.
不要把你所有的飲料都喝進去
當眾。
Don't do all your drinkin'
in public.
你不想傷害你的名字
通過愚蠢。
You don't wanna hurt your name
by being stupid.
傑姆:
最近看到你自己了嗎？
JEM:
Seen yourself lately?
我不需要。
I don't need to.
我每天早上醒來
在這肉體裡。
I wake up every morning
in this flesh.
同樣的肉,同樣的惡臭。
Same flesh, same stench.
適合我。
Suits me fine.
要知道你在生活中是誰。
Gotta know who you are in life.
錢來來去去
女性也是如此。
Money comes and goes
as does women.
由您決定
什麼樣的人
It's you who decides
what kind of man
你會的。
you're gonna be.
[海鷗吱吱叫]
[seagulls squawking]
當你的墳墓被填滿時
你的肉腐爛了...
When your grave's filled
and your flesh rots away...
你留下的一切
是你的名字。
all you leave behind
is your name.
[♪♪♪]
繼續。
Go on.
[咕嚕聲、咳嗽]
[grunts, coughs]
和你在一起更有趣
現在你喝酒了。
You're more fun to be with
now that you drink.
[咳嗽]
[coughs]
（笑）
[laughs]
[鳥兒嘰嘰
[birds chirping]
[♪♪♪]
法案:
鐵匠說
我可能會在這裡找到你。
BILL:
The smithy said
I might find you here.
這個名字是威廉·瓦爾。
The name's William Warr.
[嗅探]
[sniffs]
你可以叫我,“比爾”。
You can call me, “Bill”.
我看著你打架
在森林裡。
I watched you fight
in the forest.
[咕嚕聲]
[grunts]
嗯,那個,呃...
布里頓是一隻美味的哈巴狗。
Well, that, uh...
that Britton is a tasty pug.
但。。。你舔了他
像個傻瓜。
But... you licked him
like a fool.
他累了。
He was tired.
我很幸運。
I got lucky.
你不走運。
You weren't lucky.
不,你...你打敗了一個更強者,
更有經驗的戰士
No, you... you beat a stronger,
more experienced fighter
只是我們『你的諾金』。
just usin' your noggin'.
是的。
Yeah.
你看到他們了嗎？
You see them?
是的。
Yeah.
他們是海鷗...
Them gulls...
每年,他們都建造了
它們的巢穴破裂了。
Every year, they built
their nests in them cracks.
每年,
他們他媽的被沖走了。
And every year,
they get fucking washed away.
有時。。。
Sometimes...
一個聰明的混蛋來了
只建造他的巢穴
a clever bastard comes
and only builds his nest
就在懸崖邊。
right around the cliff.
[呼氣]
[exhales]
現在,你是原始的。
Now, you're raw.
但是在一些指導下,
你可以像他們中的一員。
But with some guidance,
you could be like one of them.
好吧,除非你想工作
你一生都為一點點,
Well, unless you wanna work
all your life for a pittance,
渾身是屎和黑煙。
covered in shit and black smoke.
我是鐵匠。
I'm a blacksmith.
我很好。
I'm fine.
那你為什麼穿越
那根繩子？
Then why did you cross
that rope?
它存在於你的血液中。
It's in your blood.
無論如何？
Eh?
現在,你來看我。
Now, you come and see me.
我會把你
在那片懸崖的頂部。
And I'll put you
at the top of that cliff.
[咕嚕聲]
[grunts]
[♪♪♪]
傑姆:
爺爺？
JEM:
Grandad?
爺爺？
把那瓶遞給我,小夥子。
Pass me that bottle, boy.
[咕嚕聲]
[grunts]
你要去
成為一名偉大的戰士。
You're going
to be a great fighter.
聽聽比爾·瓦爾（Bill Warr）的話。
Listen to Bill Warr.
[咳嗽]
[coughs]
他引導你了嗎？
Did he guide you?
[咳嗽]
[coughs]
盡他所能。
As far as he could.
哦,他不是一個好的傾聽者
就像你一樣。
Oh, he was not a good listener
like you are.
你是怎麼變成這個樣子的？
How did you end up like this?
我們生來孤獨。
We are born alone.
我們孤獨地死去。
And we die alone.
但你並不孤單。
But you're not alone.
我在這裡。
I'm here.
每個人都是孤獨的,傑姆。
Every man is alone, Jem.
現在由您決定...
It’s up to you now...
你是家裡的男人。
you're the man of the house.
你是那個會把
桌子上的麵包。
You're the one that would put
bread on the table.
別擔心我。
Don't worry about me.
我會很好的。
I'll be good.
我會很好,很好。
I'll be good, good.
[♪♪♪]
[顫抖地呼吸]
[breathes shakily]
瑪麗:
有憐悯和憐悯
在我父親的靈魂上。
MARY:
Have compassion and thy mercy
on my father's soul.
原諒他,他的罪...
Forgive him, his sins...
並許我們可以見到他...
and grant that we may see him...
在喜悅中
永恆的光明...
in the joy
of eternal brightness...
那就是主基督。
that is Christ the Lord.
[♪♪♪]
法案:
現在,看,所有人才
可以是自然的。
BILL:
Now, look, all talent
can be natural.
但控制需要學習。
But control needs to be learned.
這就是這個地方
你將學習控制。
And this is the place
you'll learn control.
[嗅探]
[sniffs]
但在我們去那裡之前,
But before we go there,
你需要知道
是什麼讓你來到這裡。
you need to know
what brought you here.
你是什麼意思？
What do you mean?
好吧,你的血。
Well, your blood.
你的曾祖父
是詹姆斯·菲格。
Your great grandfather
was James Figg.
你知道,父親
戰術戰鬥。
You know, the father
of tactical fighting.
[嘲笑]你得到了
一些最好的哈巴狗
[scoffs] You got
some of the best pugs
通過你的血管泵送,孩子。
pumpin' through your veins, boy.
現在,傑克...
Now, Jack...
他是一個可怕的擊球手。
有一個像他媽的石頭一樣的下巴。
he was a monstrous hitter.
Had a jaw like a fucking rock.
你知道,但他不會訓練。
You know, but he wouldn't train.
沒有紀律。
Had no discipline.
但最好的事情
是人群他媽的愛他。
But the best thing
was crowds fuckin' loved him.
他幾乎不是一個乞丐。
He was hardly a bev.
感謝上帝,你有
媽的樣子,你知道嗎？
Thank God, you've got
your mother's looks, you know?
[輕輕地咕嚕咕嚕]
[grunts softly]
做什麼看
與戰鬥有關』？
What do looks
have to do with fightin'?
[笑]
[chuckles]
你很快就會發現。
You'll soon find out.
[輕輕地咕嚕咕嚕]
[grunts softly]
傑克,他——他曾經喜歡
受到打擊,你知道嗎？
Jack, he-- he used to like
gettin' hit, you know?
他會用臉停止一拳。
他喜歡它。
He'd stop a punch with his face.
He loved it.
這不是不好的
為了你的外表,
It ain't no good
for your appearance,
它不是他媽的好
為了你的諾金。
and it ain't no fuckin' good
for your noggin.
我不想結束
就像他所做的那樣。
I don't wanna end up
the way he did.
他是個脾氣暴躁的老混蛋,
但。。。
He was a grumpy old bastard,
but...
不,你會沒事的
只要你學會控制。
No, you'll be all right
as long as you learn control.
好吧？
All right?
現在,向我展示你的立場。
Now, show me your stance.
你站立的方式。
The way you stand.
你為什麼不得到一點點
在你的腳球上？
Why don't you get a little bit
on the balls of your feet?
就是這樣。舉起雙臂。
好。轉一轉。
That's it. Put your arms up.
Good. Turn a bit.
可愛。
Lovely.
就是這樣。看著我的眼睛。
That's it. Look me in the eyes.
你看
有一些奇怪的東西。
You see,
there's something weird.
你看我的手。
You see my hands.
你看我的腳。
不要低頭。
You see my feet.
Don't look down.
你看到我的腳了嗎？
Do you see my feet?
是的。你看,眼睛
是一個人靈魂的窗戶。
Yeah. You see, the eyes
are the windows to a man's soul.
你可以讀懂他。
You can read him.
他不是不好
沒有這個。
He’s ain't no good
without this.
你不能依賴
僅憑自然能力。
You can't rely
on natural ability alone.
拳擊是一門藝術。這是一門手藝。
Boxing's an art. It's a craft.
拳擊手喜歡,嗯...像作家,
他們是獨立的。
Boxers like, um... like writers,
they stand alone.
你怎麼了？
What happened to you?
井。。。
Well...
[嘲笑]
[scoffs]
啊,好吧,你得不到
像這樣的厚蛆
Ah, well, you don't get
thick grubs like these
從只是在工廠工作,是嗎？
from just working in the mill, do ya?
三十一隻哈巴狗,不敗...
Thirty-one pugs, unbeaten...
直到門多薩。
until Mendoza.
你和丹尼爾·門多薩打過架嗎？
You fought Daniel Mendoza?
是的。
Yeah.
丹尼爾他媽的門多薩。
Daniel fuckin' Mendoza.
無論如何,這是一個故事
再來一次。
Anyway, that's a story
for another time.
你的手在哪裡？
Where’s your hand?
右。我要你做的一切...
Right. All I want you to do...
是滑倒和移動。
is slip and move.
沒有我的手？
Without my hands?
是的。
Yeah.
這是愚蠢的。
That's stupid.
-是的。
-[呻吟]
-Yeah.
-[groans]
那我為什麼要這樣做呢？
Then why am I doing it?
因為我負責。
Because I'm in charge.
你需要學會戰鬥
沒有你的手。
And you need to learn to fight
without your hands.
你應該沒有任何問題
躲開道路
You shouldn't have any problem
duckin' out the way
像我現在這樣的老人,應該嗎？
of an old man like me now, should ya?
[傑姆呻吟]
[Jem groans]
什麼？現在,移動。不要被擊中。
What? Now, move. Don't get hit.
[咕嚕聲]
[grunts]
就是這樣。躲避並移動。
That's it. Duck and move.
移動,移動。
Move, move.
[咕嚕聲]
[grunts]
美麗。
Beautiful.
就是這樣。肩膀。
That's it. Shoulders.
看,正對著我。
不要被平方掉。
Watch, square on me.
Don't be squared off.
可愛。可愛,可愛,可愛。
Lovely. Lovely, lovely, lovely.
[咕嚕聲]
[grunts]
[♪♪♪]
[傑姆嘲笑]
[Jem scoffs]
我們什麼時候離開？
When do we leave?
哦！別急。
Ooh! Hold your horses.
邀請已發出
一直以來
Invitations are sent out
all the time
對於嶄露頭角的戰士,
你知道,為了一個輕鬆的勝利。
to up-and-coming fighters,
you know, for an easy win.
我的意思是,冠軍的強硬
他不敗。
I mean, the champion's tough
and he's unbeaten.
他是一個骯髒的戰士。
And he's a dirty fighter.
我不在乎。我準備好了。
I don't care. I'm ready.
-我會不惜一切代價。
-嗯,他不是沒有哈巴狗。
-I'll do whatever it takes.
-Well, he ain't no pug.
他是冠軍。
He's a champion.
錢包是什麼？
What's the purse?
-一百。
-[輕輕地笑]
-One hundred.
-[chuckles softly]
右。聽。
這就是它的工作方式。
Right. Listen.
This is how it's gonna work.
我們必須把它切下來
中間,50-50。
We gotta cut it right down
the middle, 50-50.
任何費用
出來你的錢包。交易？
Any expenses
comes outta your purse. Deal?
-成交。
-好。
-Deal.
-Good.
[雨拍]
[rain pattering]
-[比爾咕嚕咕嚕]
-[吉利喘息]
-[Bill grunting]
-[Gilly gasps]
[笑]
[chuckles]
傑姆,他們是
那你打架的衣服呢？
Jem, are them
your fightin' clothes then?
當然不是,吉莉。
Of course, not, Gilly.
這就是他們都穿的衣服
在倫敦。不是嗎,比爾？
This is what they all wear
in London. Ain't it, Bill?
-是的。嗯嗯嗯。
-[吉利咯咯笑]
-Yeah. Mm-hmm.
-[Gilly giggles]
你看起來像奎爾諾布斯船長。
You look like Captain Queernobs.
[所有笑聲]
[all chuckles]
這很時髦。
It's fashionable.
-不是嗎？
-如果你是法國人。
-Ain't it?
-If you're French.
[所有笑聲]
[all chuckles]
呵呵,是浪費布料
如果你問我。
Oh, it's a waste of cloth
if you ask me.
-給他看報紙。
-哦,是的。
-Show him the paper.
-Oh, yeah.
讓你看起來
像一個合適的紳士。
Make you look
like a proper gentleman.
[笑]
[chuckles]
嘿,傑姆,看看這個。
Hey, Jem, look at this.
哦。
Oh.
甚至不要看起來像你。
Don't even look like you.
是的。這是,呃,很難
以捕獲
Yeah. It's, uh, difficult
to capture
如此驚人的美麗。
such a staggering beauty.
[所有笑聲]
[all chuckle]
“年輕的傑姆·貝爾徹。
"Young Jem Belcher.
未搗碎的。
Unbeaten.
為冠軍而戰
英格蘭。
Fighting for the championship
of England."
法案。
Bill.
瑪麗。
Mary.
好吧。
All right.
[比爾清嗓子]
[Bill clears throat]
快。
Quick.
我會看到你出來的,傑姆。
I'll see you out, Jem.
[♪♪♪]
[嘲笑]
[scoffs]
你不知道
你在做什麼。
You don't know
what you're doing.
你最終會掉進排水溝
像你的祖父
You'll end up in the gutter
like your grandfather
沒有什麼可以展示的。
with nothing to show for it.
我不喜歡他,媽媽。
I ain't like him, Ma.
永遠不會。
Never will be.
同樣的詛咒之路。
Same path of damnation.
這是不同的。
This is different.
我們會過得更好。
We'll be better off.
我保證。
I promise.
你不知道
世界的方式,傑姆。
You don't know
the ways of the world, Jem.
為賭徒而戰。
Fighting's for the betting man.
像我們這樣的人只會輸。
People like us only lose.
那不是真的,馬。
That's not true, Ma.
你錯了。
You're wrong.
[瑪麗抽泣]
[Mary sobbing]
[模糊的喋喋不休]
[indistinct chatter]
[♪♪♪]
好吧,你們倫敦人。
定居。定居。
Alright, you Londoners.
Settle down. Settle down.
而現在,挑戰者
來自西部地區。
And now, the challenger
from the West Country.
傑姆·貝爾徹將戰鬥
強大的愛爾蘭冠軍,
Jem Belcher will fight
the mighty Irish champion,
石匠！
The Stonemason!
[觀眾歡呼,大笑]
[audience cheering, laughing]
女士 們。
Ladies.
[♪♪♪]
不是嗎？嗯？
Ain’t that something? Hmm?
-呼吸。
-[深吸氣]
-Breathe.
-[inhales deeply]
很好,很深。
Nice and deep.
呼吸。
Breathe.
拉什沃思勳爵:
確保捕獲
所有這一切,伊根先生。
LORD RUSHWORTH:
Make sure you capture
all this, Mr. Egan.
現在,他有一個非常危險的
左十字。
Now, he's got a very dangerous
left cross.
好吧,所以我要你搬家
向右。
All right, so I want you to move
to the right.
想讓你思考。
Want you to think.
這就是這場戰鬥獲勝的地方。
That's where the fight's won.
把你的手帕遞給我。
Pass me your handkerchief.
[♪♪♪]
[馬鄰]
[horse neighing]
-好嗎？
-那是他嗎？
-All right?
-Is that him?
嗯。
Hmm.
[觀眾歡呼、鼓掌]
[audience cheering, applauding]
[吹口哨]
[whistling]
[觀眾叫囂]
[audience clamouring]
先生們,女士們。
Gentlemen and ladies.
時機已到。
The time has come.
你準備好了嗎
事件？
Are you ready for the main
event?
[觀眾歡呼]
[audience cheering]
你知道規則。
You know the rules.
沒有兔子打,沒有咬人,
眼睛里沒有拇指。
No rabbit punching, no biting,
no thumbs in the eye.
找到的任何工具,無論大小,
您將被取消資格。
Any tools found, big or small,
you'll be disqualified.
你不會得到一分錢。
And you won't receive a penny.
如果你們中的一個人被擊倒,
If one of you gets knocked down,
你有30秒
再次站起來。
you have 30 seconds
to get back up again.
今天在座的觀眾饑腸轆
A hungry audience here today.
讓我們給他們一個展示
最好的pugilism。
Let's give them a display
of pugilism at its finest.
而不是另一場混戰。
去你的角落！
And not another dogfight.
Off to your corners!
[觀眾歡呼、鼓掌]
[audience cheering, applauding]
[觀眾叫囂]
[audience clamouring]
時間！
Time!
[咕嚕聲]
[grunts]
[傑姆呻吟]
[Jem groans]
[輕輕地咕嚕咕嚕]
[grunts softly]
[咕嚕聲]
[grunts]
移動。
Move.
[咕嚕聲]
[grunts]
[傑姆呻吟]
[Jem groans]
[咕嚕聲]
[grunts]
[呻吟]
[groans]
[觀眾歡呼]
[audience cheering]
[褲子]
[pants]
[咕嚕聲]
[grunts]
[呻吟]
[groans]
哦,不,不,不。
Oh, no, no, no.
遠離戒指！
Away from the ring!
時間。時間。時間！
Time. Time. Time!
我告訴了你什麼？
沒有兔子打拳！
What did I tell you?
No rabbit punching!
[褲子]
[pants]
-那他媽的是什麼？
-他很快。
-What the fuck was that?
-He's fast.
他會捶打你
進入他媽的地面
He'll pound you
into the fucking ground
如果你不動。
if you don't move.
看到這些了嗎？
他們是你的盾牌。
See these?
They're your shields.
右？不要讓任何事情
進入你的腦海。
Right? Don't let anything
get in your head.
這群人,
他們不是為你而來的。
This crowd,
they're not here for you.
他媽的記住了。
Fucking remember that.
現在,你保持下巴向下。
Now, you keep your chin down.
-[呼吸沉重]
-好嗎？
-[breathes heavily]
-All right?
繼續
把他他媽的塊打掉。
Go ahead,
knock his fucking block off.
[深呼吸]
[breathes deeply]
-時間！
-[咆哮,咕嚕聲]
-Time!
-[snarls, grunts]
[咕嚕聲]
[grunts]
[人群叫囂]
[crowd clamouring]
[咕嚕聲]
[grunts]
[斯皮茨]
[spits]
時間！
Time!
他媽的你,強悍。
Fuck you, tough.
[呻吟]
[groans]
裁判。
Umpire.
他們是戰士,夥計。
They're fighters, man.
讓他們戰鬥吧！
Let them fight!
更好。
Better.
當他設置自己時,
散步一下。是的？
When he sets himself,
have a little walk. Yeah?
讓他把自己燒壞。
Let him burn himself out.
現在,找到一種方法
超出檢查範圍。
Now, find a way in
beyond the check.
裁判2:
第三回合！
UMPIRE 2:
Round three!
把他的陰道蹬掉。
Jab his puss off.
[深呼吸]
[breathes deeply]
時間！
Time!
[觀眾歡呼]
[audience cheering]
[兩個咕嚕聲]
[both grunts]
做你的回合。
Do your rounds.
-[賭博咕嚕聲]
-[咕嚕聲]
-[Gamble grunts]
-[grunts]
[賭博呻吟]
[Gamble groans]
[嗅探]
[sniffs]
-[賭博咕嚕聲]
-[傑姆咕嚕聲]
-[Gamble grunts]
-[Jem grunts]
[呻吟]
[groans]
[咕嚕聲]
[grunts]
[呻吟]
[groans]
[觀眾呻吟]
[audience groans]
-[笑聲]
-是的。掐 滅。
-[chuckles]
-Yeah. Snuffed.
[呻吟]
[groans]
[觀眾歡呼]
[audience cheering]
獲勝者,來自布裡斯托爾,
年輕的傑姆·貝爾徹！
The winner, from Bristol,
young Jem Belcher!
[觀眾歡呼]
[audience cheering]
[咯咯笑,尖叫]
[chuckles, screams]
[♪♪♪]
幹的好。
Well done.
這將使首頁
遍布全國。
This will make the front page
across the whole country.
是的！
Yeah!
[模糊的喋喋不休]
[indistinct chatter]
華麗的展示。
Magnificent display of pugilism.
謝謝你,我的主。
Thank you, my lord.
並邀請我們
進入你的...
And for inviting us
into your...
-很棒的家。
-是的。
-wonderful home.
-Yeah.
[笑]英格蘭冠軍。
[chuckles] Champion of England.
隨時歡迎
在阿什福德莊園。
Always welcome
at the Ashford estate.
任何你可能想要的,
我的僕人會答應的。
Anything you may want,
my servants will oblige.
我的主。
My lord.
[咯咯笑,深呼吸]
[chuckles, breathes deeply]
嗯。
Hmm.
我們該怎麼辦？
What do we do?
井。。。
Well...
[清嗓子,喃喃自語]
[clears throat, mumbles]
[笑]
[chuckles]
你聽到了嗎,比爾？
我們想要的任何東西。
You hear that, Bill?
Anything we want.
是的。他媽的無味。
Yeah. Fucking tasteless.
[嘉賓鼓掌]
[guests applauding]
-哦。
-這適合我們嗎？
-Oh.
-Is that for us?
謝謝。
Thank you.
先生們,我會很榮幸的
Gentlemen, I would be honoured
如果你要加入我
喝一杯。
if you were to join me
for a drink.
欽,欽。
Chin, chin.
-是--是熱嗎？
-一個有趣的想法。
-Is it-- is it hot?
-An interesting idea.
但是,唉,沒有。
But alas, no.
我的意思是,這到底是怎麼回事？
I mean, what's all this?
-這是眼睛的把戲嗎？
-沒有技巧。
-Is it a trick with the eyes?
-No trick.
特別的東西
來自法國的敵基督。
Something special
from the Antichrist in France.
他們稱之為「香檳」。
They call it “champagne”.
香檳酒。
Champagne.
想試試嗎？
Care to try?
是的。
Yeah.
我不相信我們有
適當的介紹。
I don't believe we've had
a proper introduction.
我是拉什沃思勳爵。
I am Lord Rushworth.
快樂。
Pleasure.
請。
Please.
[遠處笑的女人]
[woman laughing in distance]
我們會像皇帝一樣醉酒
We'll be as drunk as emperors
沉迷於一些之後
這些小寶貝。
after indulging in a few
of these little darlings.
-純粹的願望...
-這裡。
-A mere aspiration...
-Here.
...更多
富有想像力的農民。
...for the more
imaginative peasant.
無死刑判決
比貧困更確定。
No death sentence
more certain than poverty.
我必須說,你今天的展示
令人眼花繚亂。
I must say, your display today
was dazzling.
它花了我一分錢。
And it cost me a pretty penny.
您展示了一種新穎的精度
手腕和肩膀。
You showed a novel precision
of the wrist and shoulder.
你到底是怎麼管理的
這樣的壯舉？
How on earth did you manage
such a feat?
浮動圓形
與冠軍拉什沃思。
Floating round
with the champion, Rushworth.
沒過多久,是嗎？
Didn't take you long, did it?
如你所知,我有
對贏家的偏好。
As you know, I have
a predilection for winners.
特別是,當它們出現時
無處不在。
Especially, when they appear
from nowhere.
布裡斯托爾並非無處可去。
Bristol ain't nowhere.
4,045 海裡
4,045 nautical miles
來自甘蔗
事實上,牙買加。
from the sugarcanes
of Jamaica in fact.
拉什沃思問候戰士
Rushworth regards fighters
作為賺錢的工具
沒有其他值。
as a money-making apparatus
with no other value.
我只是相信
當一個人獲勝時,
I simply believe
that when one man wins,
另一個輸了。
刺激,就像它一樣,
another loses.
The thrill, as it were,
在一邊
的勝利者。
is being on the side
of the victor.
你不同意嗎,傑姆？
Wouldn't you agree, Jem?
[咕嚕咕嚕]我願意。
[gulps] I do.
那麼我是誰不同意
Then who am I to disagree
與新冠軍
英格蘭？
with the new champion
of England?
當然,現在,咕嚕咕嚕
一直在附近
Now, of course, pugilism
has been around
自古希臘人以來,
since the ancient Greeks,
當它是一項運動時
自然美景
when it was a sport
of natural beauty
或一種藝術形式,
而且可能還會再來。
or an artform,
and could be again.
所有上帝的受造物
傢俱齊全
All God's creatures
are furnished
帶附屬物
為了保護他們。
with appendages
for their protection.
那麼,為什麼不把它們變成
進入盈利工具？
So, why not turn them
into instruments of profit?
但每一個戰士
應該領先一步...
But every fighter
should be one step ahead...
所以他可以把這個
成為一項適當的運動。
so he can turn this
into a proper sport.
你很安靜吧,
阿什福德勳爵。
And you're quiet right,
Lord Ashford.
它應該被查看
作為一種藝術形式。
It should be viewed
as an artform.
我完全同意你的看法。
I couldn't agree with you more.
我會幫忙安排
你的下一場戰鬥,傑姆。
I will help arrange
your next fight, Jem.
這個城市沒有門
這是對領主關閉的。
There isn't a door in this city
that's closed to a lord.
是的,嗯,這是非常善良的
你的主啊。
Yeah, well, that's very kind
of you, my lord.
但我們現在還好。
But we're fine for now.
當機會來敲門時,
必須回答。
When opportunity knocks,
one must answer.
[模糊的喋喋不休]
[indistinct chatter]
說到機會...
Speaking of opportunity...
法案。
Bill.
對不起。
Excuse me.
他就像一條狗
與兩隻公雞。
He's like a dog
with two cocks.
[笑]
[chuckles]
[模糊的喋喋不休]
[indistinct chatter]
致以最良好的祝願
給你可愛的妻子。
Give my best wishes
to your lovely wife.
祝你一切順利,
阿比蓋爾夫人。
And all the best to you,
Lady Abigail.
謝謝。
Thank you.
貝爾徹先生。
Mr. Belcher.
-如何。
-是的。
-Come.
-Yeah.
[笑]
[chuckles]
所以。。。
So...
這是你的第一次曝光
上流社會？
is this your first exposure
to high society?
是的。
It is.
好吧,派對的意思是
為了愛爾蘭人。
Well, the party was meant
to be for the Irishman.
但。。。
But...
不確定他感覺到
就像慶祝一樣。
not sure he felt
like celebrating.
[笑]
[chuckles]
你——你看到了這場戰鬥嗎？
You-- you saw the fight?
嗯,真的。
Well and truly.
是否不允許女性進入
在這樣的活動中？
Are women not permitted
at such events?
[尷尬地笑]
是的,當然。我的意思是。。。
[chuckles awkwardly]
Yes, of course. I mean...
通常,我...明白了
不同類型的女性
usually, I... I see
a different type of women
在...戰鬥。
at the... fight.
[笑]我的意思是。。。井。。。
[chuckles] I mean... well...
我讓你不舒服嗎,
傑姆？
Have I made you uncomfortable,
Jem?
- 沒有。
-[阿比蓋爾夫人笑]
-No.
-[Lady Abigail chuckles]
-好。
-[笑聲]
-Good.
-[chuckles]
你會感到驚訝的
有多少婦女
You'd be surprised
at how many women
享受奇觀。
enjoy the spectacle.
你會發現很多女人
在人群中。
You'll find many women
in the crowds.
你只需要注意。
You just have to take notice.
-[笑聲]
-[模糊的喋喋不休]
-[chuckles]
-[indistinct chatter]
新的冠軍玩具已經到來。
The new champ toys have arrived.
-給我一個。
-讓路。
-Get me one.
-Make way.
[咕嚕聲]
[grunts]
哇！它們看起來如此真實！
Whoa! They look so real!
[♪♪♪]
與此同時,
我們會玩得開心。
In the meantime,
we'll have some fun.
[哆嗦
[smooches]
-哦！
-Ooh!
優雅的梳妝台。
Classy dresser.
毫米。
Mm.
[咕嚕聲]
[grunts]
[哆嗦
[smooches]
[異國情調的女人呻吟]
[exotic woman moans]
[呼吸沉重]
[breathes heavily]
[異國情調的女人咯咯笑]
[exotic woman giggles]
[講西班牙文]
[speaks Spanish]
哼？
Huh?
你在喝什麼,傑姆？
What are you drinking, Jem?
給我一些。
Give me some.
[笑]
[chuckles]
田。
Champ.
[噓聲,咯咯笑]
[smooches, chuckles]
[異國情調的女人咯咯笑]
[exotic woman giggles]
[模糊的喋喋不休]
[indistinct chatter]
-時間！
-[咕嚕聲]
-Time!
-[grunts]
[人群歡呼]
[crowd cheering]
[咕嚕聲、呻吟聲]
[grunts, groans]
[尖叫,咕嚕聲]
[screams, grunts]
[模糊的喊叫]
[indistinct shouting]
（笑）
[laughs]
[咕嚕聲]
[grunts]
放鬆。
Loosen up.
[咕嚕聲、呻吟聲]
[grunts, groans]
多麼令人生畏。
How daunting.
[咕嚕聲]
[grunts]
-[嘲笑]
-[咕嚕聲]
-[scoffs]
-[grunts]
-[約翰呻吟]
-是的！
-[John groans]
-Yes!
-[傑姆咕嚕聲]
-是的。
-[Jem grunts]
-Yes.
-[人群歡呼]
-嘿！
-[crowd cheering]
-Hey!
（笑）
[laughs]
幹得好,幹得好！
Well done, well done!
[笑]
[chuckles]
我們需要更多這樣的設施。
顯示！
We need more of that.
Spectacle!
[斯皮茨]
[spits]
（笑）
[laughs]
嗯,那是一個不同的
方法,不是嗎？
Well, that was a different
approach, wasn't it?
夢幻般的奇觀。
Fantastic spectacle.
幹得好,做得好。
Well done, well done.
瓦爾先生。
Mr. Warr.
嗯。
Hmm.
（笑）
[laughs]
拉什沃思勳爵:
所以,伊根先生,
LORD RUSHWORTH:
So, Mr. Egan,
那次演示會
激發讀者的興趣？
will that demonstration
excite your readers?
伊根:
的確,我的主啊,它會的。
EGAN:
Indeed, my lord, it will.
[拉什沃思笑]
[Rushworth laughs]
碼頭賣家:
新鮮麵包！
DOCK SELLER:
Fresh bread!
快來拿你的新鮮麵包吧。
Come and get your fresh bread.
走吧,挺身而出。給你。
Go on, step up. There you go.
有兩個給你,親愛的。
There’s two for you, darling.
男孩:
他們在那兒。
這是傑姆的媽媽。
BOY:
There they are.
It's Jem's mum.
碼頭賣家:
新鮮麵包,有人嗎？
DOCK SELLER:
Fresh bread, anyone?
來吧,大家。新鮮麵包。
Come on, everyone. Fresh bread.
新鮮麵包,女士們？
Fresh bread, ladies?
你必須為你的孩子感到驕傲,
瑪麗。
You must be proud of your boy,
Mary.
傑姆·貝爾徹。
英格蘭冠軍。
Jem Belcher.
Champion of England.
他擊敗了安德魯·甘布爾
黑色和藍色。
He beat Andrew Gamble
black and blue.
吉莉:
是的,你是對的。
GILLY:
Yeah, you're right.
[吸氣,呼氣]
[inhales, exhales]
毫米。
Mm.
英格蘭冠軍？
Champion of England?
在這裡,馬。
Here, Ma.
是什麼讓你花了這麼長時間？
What's taking you so long?
我只是習慣了它。
I'm just getting used to it.
這真的非常簡單。
It's really very simple.
你打賭支票
在你最好的五張牌上。
You bet the checks
on your best five cards.
發明一個遊戲有什麼用
What use is it to invent a game
只是為了讓它被取締
幾年後？
only to have it outlawed
a few years later?
[笑]你期待什麼？
[chuckles] What do you expect?
這就是你的法語。
That's the French for you.
他們所做的一切都是倒退的。
Everything they do is backwards.
你猜誰
會是你的下一個對手嗎？
Who do you suppose
will be your next opponent?
這取決於誰還剩下。
That depends on who's left.
戒指煥發活力
英國生活。
The ring has invigorated
English life.
你永遠不會找到的生活
在威廉·華茲華斯。
A life you'll never find
in William Wordsworth.
格鬥提供梯子
讓一個窮人成為王子。
Fighting provides a stepladder
for a pauper to become a prince.
我同意。但讀詩不容小覷
I agree. But reading poetry should not be discounted
作為一個值得追求的追求。
as a worthy pursuit.
我承認我自己
有相當多的愛好
I confess that I myself
have quite a penchant
為了華茲華斯先生。
for Mr. Wordsworth.
-丹迪斯也是如此。
-（笑）
-So do Dandies.
-[laughs]
很快,就會有排名
和重量等級。
Soon, there will be ranks
and weight classes.
男性需要到達
並獲得一定水準
Men will need to reach
and earn a certain level
在挑戰任何人之前。
before challenging anyone.
是的,一場戰鬥就是一場戰鬥,伊根。
Yes, a fight's a fight, Egan.
讓我們不要陷入困境
在技術細節上。
Let's not get bogged down
in technicalities.
[笑]
[chuckles]
關於這一點。
On that note.
[阿什福德笑]
[Ashford chuckles]
我以為你只是
習慣它。
I thought you were just
getting used to it.
哦！倍。
Oh! Fold.
我出去了。
I am out.
我們是否應該提高賭注
在最後一輪之前？
Shall we raise the stakes
before the last turn?
你知道嗎
這不值得。
You know what,
it's not worth it.
他像國王一樣打賭。
He bets like the king.
勝利和失敗在等待中
並排。
Victory and defeat lie in wait
side by side.
[傑姆咂嘴]
[Jem smacks lips]
總而言之,我的主。
All in, my lord.
我會加入你的。
I'll join you.
-哦！
-[笑聲]
-Oh!
-[chuckles]
國王很少被打敗。
Kings are rarely beaten.
但王牌勝過國王。
幹的好。
But the ace trumps the king.
Well done.
[砰砰聲]
[thumping]
伊根:
非常好。非常好。
EGAN:
Very good. Very good.
-[阿什福德夫人咯咯笑]
-再一輪,拜託,傑瑞。
-[Lady Ashford chuckling]
-Another round, please, Jerry.
你的主宰,我能有一個...
請問一個私人詞？
Your lordship, could I have a...
a private word, please?
吐出來。
Spit it out.
傑瑞:
是的,我的主。
我。。。我確實乞求你的原諒。
JERRY:
Yes, my lord.
I... I do beg your pardon.
這隻是您的信用額度
相當高
It's just your line of credit
is rather high
並超過其極限。
and over its limit.
[清嗓子]
[clears throat]
你是想讓我難堪嗎？
Are you trying to embarrass me?
不。一點也不。只是——
No. Not at all. It's just--
-[扼流圈]
-可憐的敗類。
-[chokes]
-Pitiful scum.
我可以把這個地方燒掉
今晚
I could burn this place down
tonight
沒有人會給
兩個他媽的！
and no one would give
two fucks!
停止它,拉什沃思。
Stop it, Rushworth.
我不是故意要冒犯你,
我的主啊,我發誓。
I didn't mean to offend you,
my lord, I swear.
阿什福德勳爵:
你真可惜,先生。
LORD ASHFORD:
Shame on you, sir.
這不是行為
成為一名軍官
This is not the conduct
becoming an officer
在陛下的海軍中,
退休與否。
in His Majesty's Navy,
retired or not.
嗯。
Hmm.
[馬鼻涕]
[horse snorts]
[模糊的喋喋不休
在背景中]
[indistinct chatter
in background]
[馬鼻涕]
[horse snorts]
[遠距離歡呼的男人]
[men cheering in distance]
[模糊的喋喋不休]
[indistinct chatter]
這是我的。
Here's to me.
[眼鏡叮噹聲]
[glasses clink]
[含糊不清]
[speaks indistinctly]
[笑]
[chuckles]
一定是興奮劑』,
看到新的地方。
Must be excitin',
seein' new places.
是的,它是。
Yeah, it is.
湯姆和吉莉問你
好多。
Tom and Gilly ask about you
a lot.
[遠處的鳥兒啁啾聲]
[birds chirping in distance]
如今,無論我走到哪裡
有人問你。
Everywhere I go nowadays
someone asks about you.
我想念他們。
I miss them.
我也想念你。
I miss you, too.
你可以回家了
任何時候你想要。
You can come back home
whenever you want.
你知道的,不是嗎？
You know that, don't you?
是的。
Yeah.
[歎息]
[sighs]
我錯過了什麼？
What'd I miss?
[吹拳]
[blowing punches]
有人要注意嗎？
Anyone to watch out for?
嗯,總有人
值得一看。
Well, there's always someone
worth watchin' out for.
只要我保持溫寧'
還有什麼重要的事情？
As long as I keep winnin',
what else matters?
[砰]
[thump]
這是幹什麼用的？
What's that for?
冠軍或挑戰者,
你準時出現在我的營地。
Champion or challenger,
you turn up on my camp on time.
我是冠軍。
I am the champion.
這對你來說還不夠嗎？
Ain't that enough for you?
井
你要做出選擇。
Well,
you're gonna make a choice.
你要麼像冠軍一樣訓練
You either train like a champion
或者你準備成為一個失敗者。
or you get ready to be a loser.
[吹拳]
[blowing punches]
[歎息]
[sighs]
這是第一次
你叫我失敗者,比爾。
That's the first time
you've called me a loser, Bill.
[歎息]
[sighs]
[吹拳]
[blowing punches]
[♪♪♪]
歡迎來到法孚。
Welcome to Fives.
那麼,場合是什麼呢？
So, what's the occasion?
慶祝富裕的,
富人,
Celebration of the well-heeled,
the wealthy,
和不動不動
我們的狀態。
and the immovability
of our status.
-[笑聲]
-我明白了。
-[chuckles]
-I see.
等級制度無處不在。
Hierarchies exist everywhere.
它們是一個自然的過程
的生活。
They're a natural course
of life.
這是你的理論嗎,我的主？
Is that your theory, My Lord?
呃,不是理論,而是事實。
Uh, not a theory, but a fact.
你只需要看看
在動物王國,嗯,
You need only look
at the animal kingdom, hmm,
已調整為狀態
以同樣的方式,我們是一樣的。
that are tuned to status
in the same way we are.
我們被造就以這種方式生活。
We are made to live this way.
我希望你喜歡。
I do hope you're enjoying.
我們生活在一個黃金時代,
傑姆。
We are living in a golden age,
Jem.
沒有比這更好的時間了
活著。
There's no better time
to be alive.
-嗯？
-[咕嚕聲]
-Hmm?
-[grunts]
拉什沃思勳爵:
什麼。
LORD RUSHWORTH:
Come.
以前曾經裝過袋鼠嗎？
Ever boxed a kangaroo before?
不能說我有。
Can't say I have.
他們可能是討厭的混蛋。
They can be nasty bastards.
我和一個人打架。
I fought with one.
動物試圖踢我
在銀杏中,嗯？
The animal attempted kicking me
in the gingambobs, hmm?
你應該在某個時候嘗試一下。
You should try it sometime.
[笑]
[chuckles]
也許,我會的。
Perhaps, I will.
你知道我喜歡什麼
關於戰鬥？
You know what I love
about fighting?
什麼？
What's that?
這是唯一一項有錢的運動
是由男人做的
It's the only sport where money
is made by men doing somethin'
他們通常是
鎖起來了。
they'd ordinarily be
locked up for.
從未想過
就像以前那樣。
Never thought of it
like that before.
[玻璃叮噹聲]
[glass clinks]
我們可以實現
更偉大的事情
We can achieve
even greater things
比我們已經擁有的。
than we already have.
[笑]
[chuckles]
[含糊不清]
[speaks indistinctly]
[笑]
[chuckles]
哦！
Oh!
拉什沃思勳爵:
小心,小心！
LORD RUSHWORTH:
Careful, careful!
哇,我有,我有,我有！
Whoa, ho, ho, ho!
我可以看到冠軍
英格蘭
I can see the champion
of England
採取他的休閒活動
非常認真。
takes his leisure activities
very seriously.
請允許我介紹,
新鮮格鬥前景,
May I present,
fresh fighting prospect,
亨利·皮爾斯。
Henry Pearce.
傑姆·貝爾徹。
Jem Belcher.
Jem Belcher,我是一個忠實的粉絲。
Jem Belcher, I'm a big fan.
很高興見到你,冠軍。
Pleasure to meet you, champ.
[模糊的喋喋不休
在背景中]
[indistinct chatter
in background]
同樣。
Likewise.
我們應該繼續玩得開心嗎？
在球場上,嗯？
Shall we continue with the fun
on the court, hmm?
女士們,先生們,我自己,
大人
Ladies and gentlemen, myself,
Your Lordship
挑戰冠軍
英格蘭
has challenged the champion
of England
到五人制手球大戰。
to a Fives handball battle.
聚集『圓
並下注,嗯？
Gather 'round
and place your bets, hmm?
-在你之後。
-[咕嚕聲]
-After you.
-[grunts]
[鼻涕]
[sniffles]
[模糊的喋喋不休]
[indistinct chatter]
[笑]
[chuckles]
[咕嚕聲]
[grunts]
[球彈跳]
[ball bouncing]
[咕嚕咕嚕]
[grunting]
[模糊的喋喋不休]
[indistinct chatter]
[咕嚕咕嚕]
[grunting]
哦！
Oh!
-[呻吟]
-[砰]
-[groans]
-[thud]
哦！
Oh!
[傑姆呻吟]
[Jem groaning]
[大喊大叫]
[yells]
我的眼睛！
My eye!
傑姆,不要這麼大驚小怪。
Jem, don't make such a fuss.
傑姆？
Jem?
傑姆。
Jem.
[背景中的火焰噼啪作響]
[fire crackling in background]
也許你應該回家
並看到家人。
Maybe you should go home
and see the family.
你行善。
Do you good.
我很好。
I'm fine.
只需對下一個錢包進行排序即可。
Just sort the next purse.
你看不見,對吧？
You can't see, can you?
我看得還不錯。
I can see just fine.
你知道的。你知道我的意思。
You know. You know what I mean.
[杯子嘎嘎聲]
[cup rattles]
[♪♪♪]
我知道我是誰。
I know who I am.
我是Jem Belcher。
I am Jem Belcher.
我是英格蘭的冠軍。
I am champion of England.
[遠距離小跑的馬]
[horse trotting in distance]
[歎息]
[sighs]
過去幾周你的缺席
已經發出舌頭搖擺。
Your absence these past weeks
has sent tongues wagging.
我已經準備好迎接下一場戰鬥了。
I'm ready for the next fight.
我欽佩你的樂觀,傑姆,
I admire your optimism, Jem,
我們必須把事情邁出一步
一次。
we must take things one step
at a time.
就像我說的,
給我帶來挑戰者
Like I said,
bring me a challenger
我會捍衛我的頭銜。
and I'll defend my title.
我相信你會的,
I'm sure you will,
但是我有責任
提供人們想要的東西。
however I have a responsibility
to deliver what the people want.
人們想要我,
不是挑戰者。
The people want me,
not the challenger.
不要天真,傑姆。
Don't be naïve, Jem.
這是一個偉大的奇觀
人類的勇氣
This is a great spectacle
of human courage
我們正在談論。
we're talking about.
這意味著首先對其進行工程設計。
It means engineering it first.
我賣光了人群
誰付錢看我打架。
I sell out crowds
who pay to see me fight.
不僅看到你戰鬥,
Not only to see you fight,
看到你克服逆境。
see you overcome adversity.
我們正在告訴他們一個故事,
你看？
We are telling them a story,
you see?
勝利前
一定要來奮鬥。
Before victory
must come struggle.
我努力成為
英格蘭冠軍！
I struggled to become
Champion of England!
-這還不夠嗎？
-是的。
-Isn't that enough?
-Yeah.
您的故事尚未完成
得出了結論,傑姆。
Your story's not yet
reached its conclusion, Jem.
人們想要
以查看其最後一章。
People wanted
to see its final chapter.
你不會控制我。
You won't control me.
而且你無法控制
野。
And you won't control
the people.
沒有人民,傑姆,
Without the people, Jem,
你和我都什麼都不是。
you and I both are nothing.
[歎息]
[sighs]
[♪♪♪]
[模糊的喋喋不休
和背景中的笑聲]
[indistinct chatter
and laughter in background]
不用擔心
我不追求你的錢。
Don't worry,
I'm not after your money.
直接從美洲進來。
Straight in from the Americas.
比老鼠的尿更好
他們在這裡喝酒。
Better than the rat's piss
they drink here.
[呻吟]
[groans]
[珠寶叮噹聲]
[jewelry clinking]
[關門]
[door shuts]
[杯子叮噹聲]
[cups clinking]
[喘口氣]
[gasps]
[咕嚕聲]
[grunts]
[杯子叮噹聲]
[cups clink]
但？
Ma?
主耶穌,比爾是對的。
Lord Jesus, Bill was right.
你不能留在這裡。
You can't stay over here.
你在這裡做什麼？
What you doin' here?
你的眼睛怎麼了？
What happened to your eye?
[歎息]
[sighs]
無。
Nothing.
你要和我一起回家。
You're coming home with me.
傑姆:
不,我不會去任何地方。
JEM:
No, I'm not goin' anywhere.
我不會去任何地方。
I'm not goin' anywhere.
你敢！
Don't you dare!
[呼吸沉重]
[breathing heavily]
[歎息]
[sighs]
慚愧你！
Shame on you!
別打擾我！
Leave me alone!
[呼吸沉重]
[breathing heavily]
離開！
Leave!
[呼吸沉重]
[breathing heavily]
[♪♪♪]
[人群歡呼]
[crowd cheering]
[梳妝台最高層專案破碎]
[dresser-top items shatter]
[呼吸沉重]
[breathing heavily]
[馬小跑]
[horse trotting]
[馬鄰]
[horse neighs]
-[砰]
-[馬的鄰里和打呼嚕]
-[thump]
-[horse neighs and snorts]
[硬幣叮噹聲]
[coins clink]
小心。
Watch it.
（笑）
[laughing]
您認為我們追求的
你的錢,貝爾徹？
You think we're after
your money, Belcher?
偉大的傑姆·貝爾徹已經成為
一個顫抖的小懦夫
The great Jem Belcher has become
a quivering little coward
還有一匹獨眼小馬。
and a one-eyed pony.
[紅衣衛士笑]
[red coat guard laughs]
[咕嚕咕嚕]
[grunting]
[呻吟]
[groaning]
（笑）
[laughs]
[砰]
[thump]
[呻吟]
[groaning]
[砰]
[thwack]
[呻吟]
[groans]
[咳嗽]
[coughs]
沃爾特:
你還好嗎,我的朋友？
WALTER:
Are you okay, my friend?
[呻吟]
[groans]
哼？
Huh?
沃爾特:
呃,奇怪的事情發生在一個——
WALTER:
Uh, strange things happen to a--
一個男人的思想在這裡。
a man's mind in here.
[笑]不要讓
黑暗愚弄了你。
[chuckles] Don't let
the darkness fool you.
我們母親的子宮
天黑后給了我們生命。
Our mother's womb
gave us life after darkness.
從黑暗中走出九個月後
到光。
After nine months from darkness
to light.
呃。
Uh.
♪ 我會愛你
全天 ♪
♪ And I would love you
all the day ♪
♪ 每晚
與親吻和玩耍 ♪
♪ Every night
with kiss and play ♪
[咕嚕聲]
[grunts]
[歎息]
[sighs]
[按鍵叮噹聲]
[keys jingling]
[歎息,鼻涕]
[sighs, sniffles]
這就是你所得到的一切』,
所以讓它持續下去。
That's all you're gettin',
so make it last.
[按鍵叮噹聲]
[keys jingling]
[門吱吱聲]
[door squeaks]
[通過灌籃]
[door slams]
哦！
Oh!
“英格蘭的新冠軍,
"The new champion of England,
一個亨利
“遊戲雞”皮爾斯,
one Henry
'The Game Chicken' Pearce,
享受他新發現的名聲
和財富
enjoys his new found fame
and fortune
在主持下
拉什沃思勳爵
under the auspices
of Lord Rushworth
在公司里,無論是高還是低。
in company both high and low."
所以說
非常精細的皮爾斯·伊根,
So says
the very fine Pierce Egan,
無與倫比的體育作家。
sportswriter without equal.
[嘲笑]
[scoffs]
[深吸一口氣]
[takes a deep breath]
[咕嚕聲]
[grunts]
傑克:在生活中,
JACK:In life,
不知道一個給兩個狗屎
關於你。
don't no one give two shits
about you.
[大喊大叫]
[yells]
[褲子]
[pants]
[咕嚕聲]
[grunts]
[呼吸沉重]
[breathing heavily]
我看到黑暗
不再嚇唬你。
I see the darkness
no longer scares you.
[笑]
[chuckles]
[呼吸沉重]
[breathing heavily]
恐懼可以改變
最頑固的生物。
Fear can change
the most stubborn creatures.
[咕嚕聲]
[grunts]
呃,你——你沒有道理,
老人。
Uh, you-- you make no sense,
old man.
[呼吸沉重]
[breathing heavily]
呃,嘿,年輕人,
你能來嗎——
Uh, hey, young man,
can you come--
來這裡一會兒。
come here a moment.
是的,只是一會兒。
Yes, just a moment.
[呼吸沉重]
[breathing heavily]
呃。
Uh.
不,照鏡子。
No, look into the mirror.
看著你的眼睛。
Look into your eyes.
看看有什麼在盯著你。
See what's staring back at you.
僅自己。
It's just me.
不,我說的是“什麼”,而不是“誰”。
No, I said "what", not "who".
是的。就是這樣。
Yes. That's it.
自我憎恨
正盯著你。
Self-hatred
is staring back at you.
自律
Discipline yourself
在瑣碎中
生命第一,
in the trivialities
of life first,
那麼所有事情都更重要
比這將隨之而來。
then all matters greater
than this will follow.
只有上帝決定
這個世界的悲哀和不幸,
And only God determines
the weal and woe of this world,
但人控制著自己的思想,
but man controls his own mind,
做好準備
為了任何這樣的命運風暴
readying yourself
for any such tempest of fate
這可能會炸毀你的方式。
that may blow your way.
唯一應該權衡的責任
The only blame that should weigh
在你的肩膀上,年輕人,
是自我忽視。
upon your shoulders, young man,
is that of self-neglect.
現在,你必須擁抱——
Now, you must embrace--
擁抱主權
你自己的思想。
Embrace the sovereignty
of your own mind.
[歎息]
[sighs]
你有任何人在等你
在外面？
You have anybody waiting for you
on the outside?
家庭。
Family.
[鼻涕]
[sniffles]
但是他們並不期待我。
But they're not expecting me.
誰在等你？
Who's waiting for you?
沒有人特別。
No one in particular.
只有死亡。
Only death.
[歎息]
[sighs]
[客流量]
[footfalls]
[按鍵叮噹聲]
[keys jingling]
[門解鎖]
[door unlocks]
[歎息]
[sighs]
您的債務已經還清,
貝爾徹。
Your debt has been paid,
Belcher.
[歎息]
[sighs]
沃爾特。
Walter.
沃爾特在哪裡？
Where's-- where's Walter?
那個老混蛋？
That old bastard?
他受苦的時間已經夠長了。
He suffered long enough.
加油！剁,
Come on! Chop, chop!
是的。沃爾特。
Yes. Walter.
他怎麼了？
What happened to him?
[雨拍]
[rain pattering]
[歎息]
[sighs]
[抽泣]
[sobs]
一切都會好起來的。
It'll be all right.
[歎息]
[sighing]
傑姆:
讓我們深入研究一下。
JEM:
Let's dig in.
[傑姆歎息]
[Jem sighs]
你知道,你已經變成了
相當英雄『在這裡。
You know, you've become
quite the hero 'round here.
不確定我感覺像一個。
Not sure I feel like one.
[陶器咔噠聲]
[crockery clatters]
是什麼讓你花了這麼長時間
回來？
What took you so long
to come back?
我不知道。
I don't know.
好吧,我們永遠不會過得去
沒有你。
Well, we never would've got by
without you.
你知道,沒有合適的食物,
新衣服。
you know, no proper food,
new clothes.
我的意思是,即使是新鞋。
I mean, even new shoes.
我很高興你回家了。
I'm glad you came home.
我們都是。
We all are.
那我能看到你的眼睛嗎？
Can I see your eye then?
瑪麗:
哦,吉利,別傻了。
MARY:
Oh, Gilly, don't be silly.
沒關係,她能看到。
It's okay, she can see it.
-[笑聲]
-仍然得到我的好一個。
-[chuckles]
-Still got my good one.
是真的嗎
倫敦的女士們
Is it true
that the ladies in London
穿上不同的衣服
每天？
have a different dress
every day?
是的,可能。
Yeah, probably.
倫敦是一個大集市。
London's a big fairground.
你可以玩得開心,享受它,
You can have fun and enjoy it,
但太多了
會讓你感到噁心。
but too much
can make you feel sick.
[笑]
[chuckles]
我想去那裡。
I wanna go there.
[笑]
[chuckles]
這是怎麼？
What is this?
是蘆筍。
It's asparagus.
這是他們在倫敦吃的東西。
It's what they eat in London.
[水波紋]
[water rippling]
洗手...
Wash your hands...
在鹽水中
每次戰鬥后。
in salted water
after each fight.
這樣你就可以留住他們
身體健康。
That way you keep 'em
in good shape.
[水波紋]
[water rippling]
回家真好。
It's good to be home.
[笑]
[chuckles]
“哦,主啊,
我把我的生命獻給你,
"Oh, Lord,
I give my life to you,
我信靠你。
I trust into you."
[歎息]
[sighs]
“給我看正確的道路,
哦,主。
"Show me the right path,
oh, Lord.
指
Point out
我應該走的路。
the road that I should follow.
不記得了
Not remember
悖逆的罪
我的青春。
the rebellious sins
of my youth."
[歎息]記住我...
[sighs] Remember me...
在光線下
你永不敗的愛。
in the light
of Your unfailing love.
哦,主啊。
Oh, Lord."
[♪♪♪]
[歎息]
[sighs]
[模糊的喋喋不休
和背景中的笑聲]
[indistinct chatter
and laughter in background]
湯姆:
你好。
TOM:
Oi.
-你很嘰嘰喳
-是的。
-You're chirpy.
-Yeah.
“因為我剛剛看到比爾。
'Cause I just seen Bill.
真？老屁怎麼樣？
Really? How is the old fart?
[笑]
[chuckles]
老屁想要
給你另一個機會。
The old fart wants
to give you another chance.
他不能告訴我
他自己？
He couldn't tell me that
himself?
他媽的清酒,傑姆。
Fuck sake, Jem.
這很好。
This is good.
只是 - 你只需要成為
在他位於莫寧的穀倉里。
Just-- you just gotta be
at his barn in the mornin'.
右？沒有任何藉口。
Right? No excuses.
[歎息]
[sighs]
他相信你,傑姆。
He believes in you, Jem.
我們都知道。
We all do.
我會在莫寧見到你,
是的？
I'll see you in the mornin',
yeah?
不要遲到。
And don't be late.
[♪♪♪]
將手套翻轉過來。
Turn your glove over.
給你。
快速習慣這些。
There you go.
Get used to these quick.
一切都變了
All things have changed
因為你是最後一個
在繩索前。
since you was last
in front of the ropes.
你有很多東西要學。
You got a lot to learn.
嗯？感覺如何？
Hmm? How does that feel?
[水龍頭]
[taps]
[砰]
[thump]
[咕嚕聲]
[grunts]
不,你——不,你,看——
No, you-- no, you, look--
呃,你——你他媽的慢
你他媽的軟弱！
Uh, you're-- you're fucking slow
and you're fucking weak!
我們沒有時間
他媽的錯誤。
And we ain't got time
for fuckin' mistakes.
加油。
Come on.
亨利·皮爾斯很兇猛
Henry Pearce is ferocious
他會敲一個他媽的洞
在你裡面！
and he'll knock a fuckin' hole
in you!
你必須更加努力地工作
比你他媽的工作
You gotta work harder
than you've ever fucking worked
在你的生活中！
in your life!
工作！
Work!
[咕嚕聲]
[grunts]
這是行不通的。
That won't work.
推動你他媽的自我。
Push your fuckin' self.
來吧,工作。
Come on, work.
一次機會。
One chance.
你像我母親一樣奔跑。
You're running like my mother.
但你必須問問自己
你真的想要這個嗎？
But you gotta ask yourself
do you really want this.
是嗎？
它在哪裡？
Do you?
Where is it?
你必須工作,工作,
工作,工作。
You gotta work, work,
work, work.
[傑姆咕嚕咕嚕]
[Jem grunting]
[♪♪♪]
好吧,在你的腳趾上移動。
Well, move about on your toes.
就是這樣。
That's it.
我希望你進入那裡。
I want you to get in there.
哦,看到那片草地了嗎？
Oh, see that meadow?
進去
脫鞋。
Get in there,
take your shoes off.
[模糊的吟唱]
[indistinct chanting]
比爾:亨利·皮爾斯
是要追捕。
BILL:Henry Pierce
is gonna hunt down.
他要來了
尋找你。
He' gonna come
looking for you.
[歡呼]
[cheering]
你他媽的不吵架
以前沒有人喜歡他。
And you ain't fucking fought
no one like him before.
[咕嚕聲]
[grunts]
[水濺]
[water splashes]
來吧,傑姆,
我們在這裡呆了一整天！
Come on, Jem,
we've been here all day!
噓！
Shh!
-你是什麼？
-英格蘭冠軍。
-What are you?
-Champion of England.
現在,他媽的打了他。
Now, fuckin' hit him.
傷害他！
Hurt him!
[咕嚕聲]
[grunts]
-刺痛！
-[咕嚕聲]
-Jab!
-[grunts]
亨利·皮爾斯。高等。
Henry Pierce. Higher.
法案:
在你去。
BILL:
In you go.
保持警惕。
Keep on your toes.
[咕嚕聲]
[grunts]
泥漿是幹什麼的,比爾？
What's the mud for, Bill?
呃,它加強了腿部。
Uh, it strengthens the legs.
[咕嚕聲]
[grunts]
你看起來很犀利。
You look sharp.
[咕嚕聲]
[grunts]
還沒有,你沒有。
Not yet, you don't.
它不是沒有遊戲
如果你卡住了。
It ain't no game
if you get stuck.
你必須搬家。
You gotta move.
[褲子]
[pants]
來吧,搬家。
Come on, move.
[傑姆褲子]
[Jem pants]
傑姆,我們明天可以回來。
Jem, we can come back tomorrow.
你必須打穿它。
You gotta punch through it.
工作吧！
Work it!
打敗,打敗,打敗！
Beat, beat, beat!
甩掉肩膀。
Throw the shoulder.
打！打！
Beat! Beat!
現在,嘗試抓住
其中一隻藍蒼蠅。
Now, try and catch
one of them blue flies.
哪一個？
Which one?
它是藍色的。
It's blue.
[咕嚕聲]
[grunts]
推,推,推,推。砰！
Push, push, push, push. Bam!
可愛。
Lovely.
[水漣漪]
[water ripples]
[咕嚕聲]
[grunts]
[砰]
[thump]
你知道的
我怎麼稱呼這些生物？
You know
what I call these creatures?
埃及人稱他們為『他們
“尼羅河的雷霆萬鈞。
The Egyptians called 'em
"thunderer of the Nile."
-[扎普]
-[大喊大叫]
-[zap]
-[yells]
來吧,傑姆,
如果你能接受這個,
Come on, Jem,
if you can take this,
皮爾斯不會有任何東西
給你的。
Pearce won't have anything
for you.
[咕嚕聲]
[grunts]
英格蘭冠軍,
英格蘭冠軍。
Champion of England,
champion of England.
英格蘭冠軍。
Champion of England.
[咕嚕聲]
[grunts]
[水濺]
[water splashes]
[♪♪♪]
嗯。
Hmm.
[客流量]
[footfalls]
把這一切都押在了皮爾斯身上。
Betted it all on Pearce.
皮爾斯:我們等待的那一天
終於來了。
PIERCE:The day we've waited for
is finally upon us.
英勇的傑姆·貝爾徹,
The heroic Jem Belcher,
強者的孫子
傑克·斯拉克本人,
grandson of the mighty
Jack Slack himself,
將鎖定喇叭
亨利遊戲雞肉皮爾斯
will lock horns with
Henry The Game Chicken Pierce
在一場史詩般的戰鬥中
冠軍
in an epic battle
for the championship
的英國。
of the United Kingdom.
今天標誌著進化
的運動
Today marks the evolution
of the sport
並應被說成
為了子孫後代。
and shall be spoken of
for generations to come.
- 6月26日。
-[言語模糊]
-June 26th.
-[indistinct speech]
冠軍爭奪戰
在維多利亞州。
The Championship Prizefight
in Victoria.
證明年輕人
可以智勝老人,
Proving the young
can outsmart the old,
冠軍跳舞
在戒指裡...
the champion dancing
in the ring...
-[言語模糊]
-[咕嚕聲]
-[indistinct speech]
-[grunts]
不過,這將超越它。
This will top it, though.
這是被談論的
遍布全國。
It's bein' talked about
across the whole country.
-第一--
-移動你的手。
-First--
-Move your hands.
刺:
偉大的詹姆斯·菲格。
PIERCE:
The great James Figg.
然後他的孫子,
你的祖父,
Then his grandson,
your grandfather,
傑克·斯拉克。
Jack Slack.
而現在,歷史學家的墨水
準備蝕刻你的名字
And now, historian's ink
is poised to etch your name
-在其編年史上！
-你去吧,年輕人。
-in its annals!
-There you go, young man.
明天將是歷史性的一天
用於運動
Tomorrow will be an historic day
for the sport
對你來說,傑姆。
and for you, Jem.
它是新浪潮的催化劑
的智慧,
It's the catalyst of a new wave
of smart,
科學的普吉爾主義。
Scientific pugilism.
保持你的精神高漲。
Keep your spirits high.
你值得贏得這場比賽,
田！
You deserve to win this one,
champ!
[戰鬥機咕嚕聲]
[fighter grunting]
[馬的挑釁]
[horse trots]
哦,他媽的。
Oh, fuck.
[歎息]
[sighs]
哦。
Oh.
你想要什麼,
拉什沃思？
What do you want here,
Rushworth?
-這是你的主。
-哦。
-It's Lord to you.
-Oh.
還是你的記憶變得軟了？
Or has your memory gone soft?
好吧,這裡不是沒有領主。
Well, there ain't no lords here.
我們只是在這裡
We're simply here
祝願挑戰者
祝你好運,
to wish the challenger
the best of luck,
就像任何一位尊敬的紳士們在當今的自由世界中所做的那樣。
as any honourable gentlemen would in today's free world.
我們不需要運氣。
We don't need luck.
[遠處的鳥兒啁啾聲]
[birds chirping in distance]
感覺如何知道
曾經你的現在是我的？
How does it feel knowin'
what was once yours is now mine?
它不會持久。
It won't last.
你可憐的藉口
Your pitiful excuse
不會讓你沒有免費通行證
明天。
won't get you no free pass
tomorrow.
我們很相似,你和我。
We're similar, you and me.
我能看到它。
I can see it.
唯一的區別是
我會是那個走開的人
Only difference is
I'll be the one walkin' away
用一袋較重的硬幣。
with a heavier bag of coins.
我們拭目以待。
We'll see.
拉什沃思勳爵:
傑姆。
LORD RUSHWORTH:
Jem.
照顧好那隻珍貴的眼睛。
Take care of that precious eye.
[馬的挑釁]
[horse trots]
好吧
讓我們回到嫁接。
All right,
let's get back to the graft.
搬家怎麼樣？
How about moving?
傑克:當你的墳墓被填滿時
你的肉腐爛了,
JACK:When your grave is filled
and your flesh rots away,
你留下的一切
是你的名字。
all you leave behind
is your name.
[♪♪♪]
[模糊的喋喋不休
在背景中]
[indistinct chatter
in background]
[♪♪♪]
[歡呼和鼓掌]
[cheering and applauding]
[模糊的吟唱]
[indistinct chanting]
[含糊不清的歌詞]
[indistinct lyrics]
祝你好運,傑姆。
Good luck, Jem.
小心。
Be careful.
瑪麗:你知道,我忍不住了
看著你戰鬥。
MARY:You know, I can't bear
to watch you fight.
我知道你會贏的。
I know you'll win.
[歡呼和鼓掌]
[cheering and applauding]
[模糊的吟唱]
[indistinct chanting]
吉姆·貝爾徹！
Jim Belcher!
[歡呼和鼓掌]
[cheering and applauding]
過來這裡。
Come here.
[鼻涕,咕嚕聲]
[sniffles, grunts]
[歎息]
[sighs]
調整自己的節奏
並保護那隻眼睛。
Pace yourself
and protect that eye.
把他裝箱。
Box him.
不要陷入一場悶悶不樂的比賽。
Don't get into a slugging match.
要聰明。
Be smart.
你在那裡得到了一個更大的區域,
You got a the bigger area there,
所以把那個
發揮您的優勢。
so turn that
into your advantage.
然後移動。
And move.
[深吸一口氣]
[takes a deep breath]
按照我們的協定完成他。
Finish him as per our agreement.
讓它看起來不錯。
Make it look good.
[他自己]
[pats]
你想要這個嗎？
You want this?
-你想要這個嗎？
-是的。
-Do you want this?
-Yeah.
[鼻涕]
[sniffles]
[深吸一口氣]
[takes a deep breath]
繼續。
Go on.
[人群歡呼和鼓掌]
[crowd cheering and clapping]
先生
你知道新的規則。
Gentlemen,
you know the new rules.
手套就在那裡
以保護您。
The gloves are there
to protect you.
他們始終保持狀態。
They stay on at all times.
你被撞倒了,
你有10秒鐘的時間起床。
You get knocked over,
you got 10 seconds to get up.
你接受嗎？
Do you accept?
好。
Good.
觸摸手套,
讓我們好好打一架。
Touch gloves,
let's have a good fight.
亨利·皮爾斯！
Henry Pearce!
-[人群歡呼和鼓掌]
-等等。
-[crowd cheering and applauding]
-Wait.
您的真實遊戲
就是把他從懸崖上扔下去。
Your real game
is to throw him off the cliff.
[褲子]
[pants]
[人群歡呼
並鼓掌]
[crowd cheering
and applauding]
[鈴聲響起]
[bell ringing]
裁判4:
第一輪！
UMPIRE 4:
First round!
開始！
Start!
[咕嚕咕嚕]
[grunting]
-[呻吟]
-僅此而已。
-[groans]
-That's it.
[呻吟]
[groans]
使用溜冰場。
Use the rink.
[呻吟]
[groans]
幹得好。
Good job.
吉莉:
來吧,傑姆！
GILLY:
Come on, Jem!
[歡呼和鼓掌]
[cheering and applauding]
傑姆,向後拉,向後拉。
Jem, pull back, pull back.
[咕嚕咕嚕]
[grunting]
[含糊不清的言語]
[indistinct speech]
盾牌在你的前面。
Shields in your front.
盾牌。
Shields.
[咕嚕咕嚕]
[grunting]
[歡呼和鼓掌]
[cheering and applauding]
時間！時間！
Time! Time!
好吧。哇,哇,哇！
All right. Whoa, whoa, whoa!
來吧,來吧。
Come, come on.
男孩,他要去眼睛。
Boy, he's going for the eye.
不要放下你他媽的警衛。
Don't drop your fucking guard.
只要告訴他你是誰。
Just show him who you are.
[呼吸沉重]
[breathing heavily]
好吧,這些——
這些是你他媽的盾牌。
All right, these--
these are your fucking shields.
-使用它們。
-是的。
-Use them.
-Yeah.
使用它們。
Use them.
[鈴鐺叮噹聲]
[bell dings]
[歡呼和鼓掌]
[cheering and applauding]
[咕嚕咕嚕]
[grunting]
來吧,傑姆！
Come on, Jem!
[咕嚕咕嚕]
[grunting]
[歡呼]
[cheering]
捶打他。
Pound him.
[咕嚕咕嚕]
[grunting]
哇,哇,哇！時間！
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Time!
好吧！皮爾斯
到達你的角落。
All right! Pearce,
get to your corner.
法案:
加油。
BILL:
Come on.
快點,快點。坐下。
Come on, come on. Sit down.
[大喊大叫]
[yells]
[含糊不清的言語]
[indistinct speech]
加油。加油。
Come on. Come on.
[含糊不清的言語]
[indistinct speech]
[歎息]
[sighs]
繼續使用那個鉤子。
Keep using that hook.
摧毀眼睛。
Destroy the eye.
好吧。
All right.
-來吧。重點。好？
-是的。
-Come on. Focus. Alright?
-Yeah.
看著他。
Watch him.
-好。遠離角落。
-[鈴聲]
-Good. Stay out of corners.
-[bell dings]
裁判4:
第三輪！
UMPIRE 4:
Third round!
播音員:
第三輪！
ANNOUNCER:
Third round!
[咕嚕咕嚕]
[grunting]
法案:
移動。把他裝箱。
BILL:
Move. Box him.
[咕嚕咕嚕]
[grunting]
搬走！
Move off!
[咕嚕咕嚕]
[grunting]
他媽的！
Fuck!
[咕嚕咕嚕]
[grunting]
小心！
Careful!
吉莉:
來吧,傑姆！
GILLY:
Come on, Jem!
[咕嚕咕嚕]
[grunting]
好吧,好吧,
夠了,皮爾斯。
All right, all right,
enough of that, Pearce.
在另一輪中。
In the other round.
回到你的角落。
Back to your corner.
[人群成員吹口哨]
[crowd member whistling]
[模糊的吟唱]
[indistinct chanting]
[鼓掌]
[clapping]
-[歎息]
-哦。
-[sighs]
-Oh.
我看起來怎麼樣？
How do I look?
啊,你看起來像
哈利英俊。
Ah, you look like
Harry Handsome.
[一起笑]
[laughing together]
現在,這將需要
腫脹下來。
Now, this'll take
the swelling down.
[咕嚕聲]
[grunts]
不要和這個人打仗。
Do not go to war with this man.
使用這個。
Use this.
不要讓他困住你
在角落裡。
Don't let him trap you
in a corner.
把他轉過來。
Turn him.
當你裝箱時,它很漂亮。
It's beautiful when you box.
當你被堵住的時候。
When you're jammin' out.
節拍,節拍,節拍。哼？
Beat, beat, beat. Huh?
繼續。
Go on.
-[大喊大叫]
-[鈴聲]
-[yells]
-[bell dings]
裁判4:
第四回合！
UMPIRE 4:
Round 4!
[歡呼]
[cheering]
[咕嚕咕嚕]
[grunting]
[♪♪♪]
-[呻吟]
-[砰]
-[groans]
-[thump]
[歡呼鼓掌]
[cheering an applauding]
起床！
Get up!
4, 5, 6, 7.
-拉什沃思勛爵:起來！
-8, 9.
-LORD RUSHWORTH: Get up!
-拉什沃思勛爵:起來！
-[咕嚕聲]
-LORD RUSHWORTH: Get up!
-[grunts]
是的,來吧,寶貝。
Yeah, come on, baby.
[咕嚕咕嚕]
[grunting]
-是的。
-[咕嚕咕嚕]
-Yeah.
-[grunting]
[含糊不清的言語]時間！
[indistinct speech] Time!
[褲子]
[pants]
美麗,美麗。
Beautiful, beautiful.
太美了,你在打拳擊。
Beautiful, you're boxing.
你就是我們。
You're usin' that.
[歡呼]
[cheering]
阻止它。
Block that.
用你他媽的頭！
Use your fuckin' head!
你必須得到他,對吧。
你得把他趕出去,兒子。
You gotta get him, right.
You gotta get him out, son.
你必須把它們都搬來搬去。
You gotta move 'em all around.
不要讓他得到你。
Do not let him get you.
來吧,兒子。去。
Come on, son. Go.
拉什沃思勳爵:
來吧,亨利！
LORD RUSHWORTH:
Come on, Henry!
[人群歡呼]
[crowd cheering]
拉什沃思勳爵:
來吧,亨利！
LORD RUSHWORTH:
Come on, Henry!
[人群歡呼]
[crowd cheering]
[咕嚕咕嚕]
[grunting]
拉什沃思勳爵:
是的！是的！
LORD RUSHWORTH:
Yes! Yes!
[咕嚕咕嚕]
[grunting]
哦！
Oh!
[鼓掌]
[applauding]
[褲子]
[pants]
[砰]
[thump]
哦！
Oh!
拉什沃思勳爵:
哦,是的！
LORD RUSHWORTH:
Oh, yes!
[砰]
[thud]
拉什沃思勳爵:
乾的好！
LORD RUSHWORTH:
Well done!
裁判4:
1, 2, 3...
UMPIRE 4:
[咕嚕聲]
[grunts]
裁判4:
4,5,和時間！
UMPIRE 4:
4, 5, and time!
法案:
好。好。
BILL:
Okay. Okay.
是的！
Yes!
[褲子]
[pants]
幹得好,亨利,幹得好！
Well done, Henry, well done!
-培訓師:好人,幹得好。
-就是這樣！
-TRAINER: Good man, well done.
-That's it!
[咕嚕聲]
[grunts]
哦,他媽的我。
Oh, fuck me.
它掛在骨頭上,
那是。
It's hangin' off the bone,
that is.
好吧,那麼。㡲。
All right, then. Hold fast.
[骨頭濕囉音]
[bone crackles]
[呻吟]
[groans]
就是這樣。
That's it.
你現在是一個合適的戰士。
You are a proper fighter now.
啊？呼吸。加油。
Eh? Breathe. Come on.
呼吸,呼吸,呼吸。
Breathe, breathe, breathe.
你聽見了嗎,傑姆？
Did you hear me, Jem?
-嘿？
-是的。是的。
-Hey?
-Yeah. Yeah.
[呼吸沉重]
[breathes heavily]
你必須集中注意力。
You gotta focus.
[褲子]
[pants]
這些是冠軍
回合,好嗎？
These are the championship
rounds, all right?
你他媽的要控制他。
You gotta fuckin' dominate him.
這是關於誰想要你
最多,他或你。
It's about who wants you
the most, him or you.
你不會
他媽的,給你。
You ain't gonna
fuckin' give it, you.
你得他媽的拿走它。
You gotta fuckin' take it.
是的。喝點水。
Yeah. Have some water.
[誹謗]
[slurps]
告訴我,是的,
現在一切都好了。
Show me, yeah,
it’s all right now.
走吧,兒子。
Go on, son.
[咕嚕聲]
[grunts]
[大喊大叫]
[yells]
[鈴鐺叮噹聲]
[bell dings]
[歡呼]
[cheering]
[咕嚕咕嚕]
[grunting]
-[鈴聲]
-[咕嚕咕嚕]
-[bell dings]
-[grunting]
去吧,夥計！
Go, mate!
[鈴鐺叮噹聲]
[bell dings]
法案:
是的！開始吧,
開始吧,傑姆！
BILL:
Yeah! Get going,
get going, Jem!
[咕嚕咕嚕]
[grunting]
[鈴鐺叮噹聲]
[bell dings]
[歡呼]
[cheering]
[咕嚕咕嚕]
[grunting]
[鈴鐺叮噹聲]
[bell dings]
[咕嚕咕嚕]
[grunting]
乾的好！
Well done!
[咕嚕咕嚕]
[grunting]
[鈴鐺叮噹聲]
[bell dings]
[咕嚕咕嚕]
[grunting]
[歡呼和鼓掌]
[cheering and applauding]
[鈴鐺叮噹聲]
[bell dings]
幹得好,亨利！
Well done, Henry!
[鈴鐺叮噹聲]
[bell dings]
[兩個咕嚕聲]
[both grunting]
[鈴鐺叮噹聲]
[bell dings]
[觀眾歡呼]
[audience cheers]
[兩個咕嚕聲]
[both grunting]
[觀眾歡呼]
[audience cheers]
[咕嚕聲,褲子]
[grunts, pants]
關。看看我。
Off. Look at me.
[褲子]
[pants]
多少根手指
我堅持住嗎？
How many fingers
am I holdin' out?
F--f--四。
F-- f-- four.
我不知道還有多少
你可以拿走,兒子。
I don't know how much more
you can take, son.
[褲子]
[pants]
你的另一隻眼睛現在他媽的。
Your other eye's now fucked.
嗯,我沒事,
Mm, I'm okay,
呃,你一樣瞎子
作為他媽的蝙蝠。
Uh, you're as blind
as a fuckin' bat.
-我要停止這個。
-不,不,不,不,不,不,拜託！
-I'm gonna stop this.
-No, no, no, no, no, please!
拜託,拜託,比爾,拜託。
Please, please, Bill, please.
-只需去打開它。
-我不能。
-Just go and open it.
-I can't.
走吧,打開它。
來吧,拜託。
Just go, open it.
Come on, please.
-我不能。
-來吧,打開它。
-I can't.
-Come on, just open it.
請打開它！
Open it, please!
拜託,做吧,比爾。
比爾,做吧。請。
Please, do it, Bill.
Bill, do it. Please.
加油。加油。
Come on. Come on.
[噓]
[shushes]
[傑姆呻吟]
[Jem groaning]
他媽的！
Fuck!
[傑姆呼吸沉重]
[Jem breathing heavily]
[呻吟]
[groans]
[尖叫]
[screams]
好的,好的。
Okay, all right.
好吧,深呼吸。
All right, breathe deep.
[深呼吸]
[takes deep breaths]
呼吸。就是這樣。
Breathe. That's it.
很好,很穩定。
Nice and steady.
就是這樣。好吧。
That's it. All right.
[呻吟]
[groans]
就是這樣。
That's it.
喝水。
Drink water.
[誹謗]
[slurps]
[咕嚕聲]
[grunts]
[褲子]
[pants]
[觀眾歡呼]
[audience cheers]
[♪♪♪]
瑪麗:贏或輸...
我為你感到驕傲。
MARY:Win or lose...
I'm proud of you.
等等！
Wait, wait!
聽。聽。
Listen. Listen.
媽來了,這很好,
It's good your mum's here,
但你必須集中注意力
在戰鬥中。
but you gotta focus
on the fight.
是的。
Yeah.
他不會放棄。
He won't quit.
不要讓他把你切開。
Don't let him cut you open.
你又流血了,
你他媽的會死的。
You bleed anymore,
you'll be fuckin' dead.
你需要
睜開眼睛。
You need
to open his eye back up.
讓他流血。
Make him bleed.
我知道你累了,
但他也是。
I know you're tired,
but so is he.
來看看吧。
Have a look.
我會贏得公平和公正
或者根本不是。
I'll win fair and square
or not at all.
拉什沃思勳爵:
如果你不完成他
在這一輪中,你這個混蛋,
LORD RUSHWORTH:
If you don't finish him
in this round, you bastard,
我會賠一大筆錢。
I'll lose a fortune.
因著上帝,你也會如此。
And by God, so will you.
-[咕嚕聲]
-[人群驚呼]
-[grunts]
-[crowd exclaims]
觀眾:
哦,這是怎麼回事？
CROWD MEMBER:
Oh, what's going on?
[深呼吸]
[takes deep breaths]
我不會作弊的,比爾
或者他聲稱的。
I ain’t gonna cheat, Bill
or what he claim.
[歎息]
[sighs]
我的讚美,皮爾斯先生。
My compliments, Mr. Pearce.
你做榮譽
到拳擊運動。
You do honour
to the sport of boxing.
你們倆都這樣做。
Both of you do.
[人群在後台歡呼]
[crowd cheering in background]
[呻吟]
[groans]
給我看。
Show me.
[呻吟]
[groans]
我沒有感覺到我的手。
I don't feel my hand.
-[骨頭噼啪聲]
-[呻吟]
-[bones crackle]
-[groans]
它壞了,兒子。
It’s broken, son.
好。
Okay.
就是這樣。
That's it.
好吧。
All right.
[呻吟]
[groans]
聽我說。
Listen to me.
我再給你一輪,
然後我稱之為『它。
I'll give you one more round,
then I'm callin' it.
你明白嗎？
Do you understand?
是的。
Yeah.
[鼻涕]好吧。
[sniffles] All right.
[鼻涕]
[sniffles]
好吧。
All right.
[親吻]
[kisses]
好孩子。
Good boy.
是的。
Yeah.
裁判4:
女士們先生們
UMPIRE 4:
Ladies and gentlemen,
這將是最後一輪
的皮帶。
this will be the final round
of the belt.
第18回合！
Round 18!
[鈴鐺叮噹聲]
[bell dings]
裁判4:
箱。
UMPIRE 4:
Box.
[歡呼和鼓掌]
[cheering and applauding]
[咕嚕咕嚕]
[grunting]
-來吧！
-[咕嚕咕嚕]
-Come on!
-[grunting]
[♪♪♪]
是的！加油！
Yeah! Come on!
[咕嚕聲]
[grunts]
不要讓我這樣做！
Don't make me do this!
加油！打我！
Come on! Hit me!
不要讓我這樣做！
Don't make me do this!
加油！來！
Come on! Come!
你什麼都沒剩下
證明,傑姆！
You have nothing left
to prove, Jem!
做吧！加油！來！
Do it! Come on! Come!
[砰]
[thump]
[人群吟唱]
[crowd chanting]
[砰]
[thud]
[♪♪♪]
裁判4:
...七,八,九,十。
UMPIRE 4:
...Seven, eight, nine, ten.
就是這樣。
That's it.
亨利·皮爾斯仍然是
英格蘭冠軍。
Henry Pearce is still
the champion of England.
[人群歡呼,鼓掌]
[crowd cheering, applauding]
[♪♪♪]
[人群高呼,鼓掌]
[crowd chanting, applauding]
[♪♪♪]